<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Arizona Technology Consultants - Call Us @ (623)272-9715]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Arizona Technology Consultants - Call Us @ (623)272-9715]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/arizona-technology-consultants/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 17:01:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/arizona-technology-consultants/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[James and his team made a great website for our company. James was an expert and was our main point of contact. He is a great listener, and as a result of those listening skills, was able to implement the vision we had for our site to the tee. I recommend working with him to anyone!]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>James and his team made a great website for our company. James was an expert and was our main point of contact. He is a great listener, and as a result of those listening skills, was able to implement the vision we had for our site to the tee. I recommend working with him to anyone!</h1><p>Our company needed some assistance moving our website and web mail on very short notice. James provided excellent and professional service, and was able to quickly come up with a plan of action and walk us through the process so we were ready for the switch. I would definitely contact him if we needed any additional work, and I highly recommend him to anyone else looking to use his services. Personable, professional and solid service. What more could you ask for?</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/arizona-technology-consultants/testimonials/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6460d9b6-0288-4d30-92d1-789a9c9069f3</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 17:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Us</h1><p>Arizona Technology Consultants is a local business in Tempe, AZ, but serves clients throughout the Phoenix Metropolitan area. We offer web design, IT consulting, search engine optimization and much more! Founded while studying at their alma mater Arizona State University in 2004 by brothers James and Nick Kallof, are experts in web site design, social media marketing and using technology to build small businesses.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/arizona-technology-consultants/about-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8c2b6f7f-b16d-45fc-a2e8-2d82ceac48ca</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2016 17:01:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>